Last time on Zombieland Saga, we got a dance lesson from some cool old people.
But then some scary biker girls had us dancing between a rock and a hard place!
Guess I just look like an easy target!
And get this, their boss turned out to be the daughter of Saki's old ride-or-die gal pal!
Then our fearless leader cranked up a bike for the world's deadliest game of chicken!
Thanks to that, we've got some scrappy new fans!
Glad to have you guys!
Sweet, we did it! That was killer! I can already see us taking over!
Don't get carried away! I mean, I'm just saying!
Saki seems really happy now that one of her old buddies is a fan of ours!
And Lily's been bursting with energy ever since her dad started coming to see our performances!
I and Junko have been a lot more relaxed since everything that happened with the Saga Rock Festival this summer.
And me? I still don't have my memories back.
I wonder what happened in my life before I died.
Huh? A show for 500 people?
That's right. You've come very far.
Is that, like, a lot?
Duh! I mean, think. 100 times 5.
Well, we are at that point.
This'll be a first for you. You all are the main event.
Can you fill 500 seats on your own?
Well, can you, Sakura?
You'd better!
Anyway!
Anyway! You're booked at an exhibition hall in Karatsu.
The famous Furosato Hall Arpino!
Ar... Pino?
Where's that?
Glad you asked.
It's right here!
It's cute!
It feels like we're finally staking our claim in this world.
This'll be different than performing under an open sky.
Takes me back.
This is the place where my old group did our very first show in Saga.
Actually, it feels kind of familiar to me, too.
Maybe... I've been here.
Recently, this multi-purpose hall hasn't hosted many musical events.
But after we perform here, perceptions will change.
Thanks to you, Arpino will be recognized as a venue.
And you'll have completed your first step to saving Saga Prefector!
That feeling...
For some reason, I'm super excited now.
Maybe there's something about that place that has to do with my old life.
And when we perform there, I bet the memories will come rushing back.
I can't fall asleep.
I might as well get in some practice instead.
Sakura!
Huh?
Yeah?
You're getting too far ahead.
Try to keep pace with us.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Think you might need a break?
Of course I don't need a break.
I feel like I could keep practicing forever.
This is our big solo show.
We gotta make sure it's perfect, you know?
Damn, you're acting like a bigger nerd than usual.
Don't be silly.
Oh, and by the way, I had an idea while I was up all night rehearsing.
I was thinking during the hook it might be cool to throw in an extra step.
Shouldn't we focus on learning the basic pattern?
I get where you're coming from, but just let me show you real quick.
I promise you're gonna love it.
I'm not so sure.
Oh, wait.
The weather is really beautiful today.
It might be fun to practice outside for a change.
Let's go to the roof.
We can't do that.
There's no roof access.
Good morning, Fransu Sudolay.
Yee-haw.
Well, straight to business then.
In light of your big concert, you get a special training regimen.
What is that supposed to mean?
You're going to the mountains!
Uh, you can't be serious.
Like, now?
It has to be now!
You can't pull off something like this without a full-on mountain training montage!
See?
You get your butts kicked, you grow, and you return!
Hmm?
And you'll be stuck there till I come to the rescue to live!
Yee-haw!
Do you think there's any real benefit to this?
Hell if I know.
But if he's messing with us, I'm gonna punch the shades right off his face!
Looks like we're here.
Goodness.
He certainly chose a barren spot, didn't he?
If I weren't dead, I'd probably die here.
I feel like a zombie popsicle!
This really sucks.
I'm bored.
What do we do?
We can't practice in a place like this.
If we're dead, can we still freeze to death?
Not to death.
We'd be fine after we thawed out.
Assuming we didn't get eaten.
What?
Eaten?
None of us can freeze!
No one!
It's kind of late for that.
Look.
Tai!
Sure wish we had a fire.
Oh, I can make one for us?
For real?
Sure I can!
Duh!
I mean, I was the lovable star of Girl Scout Mania Case Files 3, remember?
What's that?
In the meantime, I suppose I should try to find something for us to eat.
You're right.
We won't get anything done if we're just sitting around.
Yeah.
But wait.
Shouldn't we be practicing?
We have a autopino coming up.
Yeah, but figuring out how to survive is more important.
Survive is a strong word.
I'm gonna go pick up some branches and stuff we can use as firewood.
Branches from pine trees are really good for that.
Now, now.
Let's get settled.
Then perhaps we can practice a bit.
Okay.
Check it out, squirt.
Here's more sticks than you can shake a stick at.
This is plenty, right?
Hey, don't do that!
I told you, you're supposed to let them dry out by the fire first.
Oops.
Look what I found.
These mushrooms look delightfully tasty.
Though they might be poisonous.
Who cares?
We're zombies!
Stop!
What are you doing?
I'm hunting, obviously.
Hunting?
Shh!
It's under that tree.
Please don't shoot the cute little piggy!
Sorry.
It's no big deal.
I've got a quicker ride than the others.
I'll find something else.
If you say so.
I'm gonna go take a look over there.
You in?
Uh, no.
Think I'll pass.
Sakura.
Are you trying to catch a fish?
Uh-huh.
I get to sit quietly.
So it's kind of the perfect job for me.
I see.
There's so much chaos.
Huh?
Really?
Where?
Oh, it's inside your heart, of course.
Oh.
Is there something bothering you?
Well, yeah.
I guess I just want to feel like all of us are doing the best we can.
And I think we need to practice a lot more if we want the concert to be any good.
I know you do.
But panicking won't help.
It's like when you're fishing and don't catch anything.
You wonder how deep the fish are.
Did you use the right bait?
Or maybe you picked a bad spot.
If you're calm and think about it from different angles,
you can usually find the answer, you know?
We did it!
I have to make sure I'm ready to perform at Arpino.
Even if I'm all alone.
We've been here a few days and nobody's gotten eaten yet,
so I'd say we're killing it.
But still, we've got one thing left that needs to be done.
Something that's really important.
I'm so glad!
Thank you!
I thought you guys had forgotten it.
No way!
We need meat!
And not just fish, either.
We're zombies.
We gotta have something worth catching.
I've been trying my best, but that baby boar is just so skittish.
Don't beat yourself up about it.
We're new to this.
None of us really know how to mess with wild game.
All right, let's talk about who does what.
Sure, sounds good.
Okay!
The trap's totally hidden.
Good.
He'll come by any minute now.
Are you sure about this?
He's close.
Okay, hide!
Hey, wait up!
Oh my word.
She just ruined the trap!
Saki!
Okay, don't move!
What the hell is that?
I guess he's the daddy boar!
One thing's clear.
We need a much bigger pit.
Oh no, this is about to get worse.
Oh my god!
What do I do?
This nice piggy!
Damn it!
How do we save her?
I think I might have an idea.
I learned it from a joy missionary back in Shimabara.
Listen carefully, Lady Sakura.
You need to play dead.
But she is dead.
Come on.
He chomped her head!
You okay, Sakura?
Say something!
Is this wrong?
No joke.
That thing was really disgusting.
Not the boar.
I mean this.
We're supposed to be running our dance routines,
not running away from wild animals.
We should be showered in spotlights, not drool.
There's not much time left.
So why are we spending it on pointless stuff like this?
Oh, I see now.
Found you!
The good yodel old lady day!
Lady, lady, lady!
How'd it go?
Did you learn any yodel lady, yodel lady, yodel lady life lessons?
Are you kidding?
Just look at us.
Your idiotic games won't prepare us for anything.
The big show is only days away.
I see no point being here.
I'm over it.
Don't you?
Then you should close your eyes.
And listen.
That way, dear Mother Gaia will speak.
And then you'll know!
Even up here, you are never alone!
I just said I've had enough!
Oh, my.
I'm going home!
What?
Great job.
So what's the plan?
Go home!
This is bad.
Things have been super awkward since yesterday on the mountain.
But our performance at Arpino is right around the corner.
Sakura!
At this rate, we'll be way under-rehearsed.
You're still fast.
Like I said before, you need to match our pace.
This isn't a solo.
Let's try again from the top.
It's not my fault we're out of sync.
Well, you guys were goofing off out there.
I was actually practicing our dance!
Well, that was rude.
What gives?
Welcome to…
Huh?
Greetings.
Gentlemen.
What is it you want?
Well, I am a courtesan.
You're here to dance?
I'm also trained as a geisha.
Not what I asked.
You sent all of us into the mountains,
hoping that Lady Sakura would find some inner peace before the concert.
Is that right?
The beauty of a group is that it makes up for individual weaknesses, resulting in greater collective strength.
But if Sakura can't see that, what's the point?
Indeed, sir.
But couldn't you just tell her?
It's something she needs to learn for herself.
You're different with Lady Sakura.
She must be dear to you.
I only care about saving Saga.
And I have a soft spot for those who can't express themselves.
Saga's depopulation problem is so exhausting.
Every time we climb one mountain, there's a taller one.
And now, with this show, it's like we're lost in the wild.
Listen, I'll be honest here.
I think she can do it.
That's enough foolishness, Lord Kotaro.
Mark my words, that brave girl can do anything.
Yeah, that's what I just...
You should have more faith in her.
I just said I do.
You guys heard me, right?
It just keeps getting more complicated.
How can I make this right?
I mean, no matter what, I want the concert to be great.
That venue might have some kind of connection to my past.
And performing there could be huge for us.
We have to do everything we can.
It's okay.
I know I'm in the right here.
And after we put on a good show, I'm sure they'll understand.
So everybody knows their positions now, right?
Yeah!
Alright, let's try the whole thing from the beginning.
It's funny.
I've never actually watched Franshu-shu from the outside.
Let's talk about this part.
It kind of feels like I'm standing in one place for too long.
I see.
Oh, you must mean the bit when we're across from each other.
Yeah, exactly.
Hmm.
Well, Arpino's a pretty big place.
Do you want to try spreading out farther on the sides?
Like, get this part?
Oh, good idea!
The extra space would give me and Junko more room to move, too.
That sounds great.
Hey, if you want me to, I could just switch positions.
Let's talk about this part.
Kind of feels like I'm standing in one place for too long.
I see.
Oh, you must mean the bit when we're across from each other?
Yeah, exactly.
Hmm.
Well, Arpino's a pretty big place.
Do you want to try spreading out farther on the sides?
Like, get this part?
Oh, good idea!
The extra space would give me and Junko more room to move, too.
That sounds great.
Hey, if you want me to, I could just switch positions with Tai.
Oh, I get it.
Everyone moves around Sakura.
That sounds really interesting.
Let's do it!
I love it when a plan comes together.
Let's make sure we've got it down so it'll be easy to...
These guys haven't been rehearsing at all.
So how did they get so in sync?
It must be because they pulled together to make the best of those harsh conditions.
Everyone except me.
You're back!
I'm sorry.
I've been thinking, and I see now that I was being selfish.
Ever since I found out about the Arpino show, I've just been so worked up.
I started obsessing over doing a great job and making everything perfect.
But because of that, I didn't consider you guys.
I forgot about Fran Shushu.
About our team.
Yeah, that explains it.
I thought you seemed kinda hot under the collar.
You still haven't figured it out?
Mr. Kotaro?
Think Niji no Matsubara.
A pine forest.
Pine as in Alpine.
Alpine as in the Alps.
Hence the mountains.
Mountain climbing.
Except with your issues.
I have no idea what that means.
But I'll do my best, sir.
You guys.
Okay!
Let's work hard and make this the best show ever!
Yeah!
I'm glad everything worked out.
What do you mean?
Good morning, Ai!
I'm going running!
Keep an eye out for traffic!
Okay!
There's one week left before our big solo concert.
I've got all the songs and dances memorized.
And we're totally in sync!
So I'm beyond excited!
Plus, if I step onto that stage,
maybe I'll remember something important.
And then I'll finally be able to make peace with my past life!
I know my future will be full of happiness and excitement!
Come on, Romero!
Here I go!
Oh, God!
Poor girl!
Let me check!
Go get help!
Okay, doggy?
Be right back!
Where am I?
I don't...
You!
You?!
Lily here? Ron Shushu's really become an unstoppable team! I can't wait to dazzle everyone at the big show!
Next time on Zombieland Saga Episode 11, One-of-a-Kind Saga! Don't miss it!